We pawned them, dude. Up top.
(Sheldon:)Look at him.
(Sheldon:)Wil Wheaton, my old friend.
(Sheldon:)I have chased you
around the moons of Nibia...
...and around the Antares Maelstrom,
and around Perdition's flames.
(Raj:)You keep quoting Wrath of Khan,
but he was in Next Generation.
(Raj:)-It's a totally different set of characters.
-Silence.
(Sheldon:)How much longer must I wait
for my revenge?
(Raj:)If Wil Wheaton
and Stuart win their match...
(Raj:)...and we beat Lonely Larry and
Captain Sweatpants in the next round...
...we'll face off for championship.
(Sheldon:)So my path to satisfaction is blocked
by Lonely Larry and Captain Sweatpants.
(Sheldon:)Very well, they must be destroyed.
(Raj:)Dude, you have to stop talking like that.
It's really lame.
(Sheldon:)Silence.